+62895334568841

Bachtiar Fatur Rohim

Web Developer

Fast learning on all aspect of web development including front and backend with 3 years experiences in web programming professionally. Have experience working in national and multinational companies, and accustomed to working on a project base and product base

Work Experience

MadeIndonesia - Fullstack Wordpress Developer

MARCH 2020 - CURRENT

- Become Fullstack Developer and successfully helped develop a small business into a digital business
- Develop more than 20+ projects using custom WordPress CMS, Javascript, CSS/SCSS, PHP
- Create custom plugins to handle complex projects that use Woocommerce and Mollie Payment Gateway
- Slicing a responsive web layout using HTML, CSS/SCSS, and Javascript
- Collaboratively work with the designer team and the project manager from Netherland
- Accustomed to leading projects with the frontend team
- Manage standardized coding for the developer team
- Deploy a final product to the server using FTP and Gitlab CI/CD

CronosERP - Backend Developer (Laravel)

AUGUST 2019 - MARCH 2020,

- Develop an ERP system using Laravel Framework
- Develop a 'Scrap Modules' features
- Mapping the relationships between databases and designing a more efficient system flow
- Create an interactive user interface using JavaScript and Jquery
- Work collaboratively with other divisions such as Finance and
- Working with multiple database technology such MySQL and PostgreSQL

sistemtoko.com - Web Developer Internship

INTERNSHIP | JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019.

- Create a full E-Commerce application, starting from the database design, to becoming a complete application
- Develop a bunch of applications using Laravel, Codelgniter, and ReactJS

Freelance

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

As a self-employed entrepreneur, I help clients with their cool idea into an interactive and solid web application. I mostly use Laravel Framework on my freelance project.

Education

University of Technology Yogyakarta

2017 - 2022 BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS

Learn more in the world of programming starting from basic algorithms to advanced ones using C++ and Java until be interested in web development, in the second semester deepening the world of web development using html, css and javascript. I lead a final project to finish the last semester and build HRMS to fulfill my final project in college. I took a semester leaves in my 5th semester and use it for working full-time as a web developer and continue my study on the next year while working fulltime, but I still have a good GPA score tho'.

GPA: 3.64

SMA Negri 6 Cirebon

2015 - 2017

Get to know and interest the world of programming and start learning html self-taught

Skills

Soft skills: Leadership • Problem Solving • Curious, eager to learn • Critical Thinking

Hard skills: PHP, Go, Javascript, jQuery, CSS/SCSS, HTML, WordPress, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Laravel, Vuejs, ReactJS, Git, Docker

Language: Bahasa (native) • English

Contact:



gitlab.com/MI-Bachtiar



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bachtiar-fatur-rohim-589478185/